https://git.ir/
https://git.ir/
- Something is wrong.
- یک چیزی اشتباه است !
Perhaps the users of your existing product
شاید کاربران محصول شما
are complaining on social media about poor usability.
از ضعیف بودن قابلیت استفاده از محصولات شما در شبکه های اجتماعی شکایت میکنند
Or maybe you're planning on creating something new
یا شاید شما برنامه دارید که یک چیزه جدید بسازید
and want to get it right from the start.
و میخواهید شروعی خوبی را برای آن داشته باشید
Or perhaps you have a robust user experience team already,
یا شاید شما یک تیم تجربه کاربری قوی در حال حاضر داشته باشید،
but they're the ones who are complaining about
اما آن ها کسانی هستند که در این مورد شکایت میکنند
a totally overwhelming workload.
یک حجم کار کاملا قافل گیر کننده
What you need is more user experience firepower.
چیزی که شما به آن نیاز دارید، تجربه کاربری بیشتر است
Now.
حالا
Whether you have a UX team already or not,
چه یک تیم UX داشته باشید چه نه،
your business goals may require expanding your capabilities
هدف های بیزینس شما شاید نیاز داشته باشد که قابلیت های خود را گسترش دهید
with additional skills and staff.
با مهارت ها و کارمندان بیشتر
If you're trying to figure out what kind of help you need,
اگر سعی میکنید که متوجه شوید که چه نوع کمکی نیاز دارید،
what kind of specialties exist
چه نوع تخصص هایی وجود دارد
or whether your needs require permanent placement
یا اینکه نیازهای شما به قرارگیری دائمی نیاز دارد یا خیر
or limited contracting resources,
یا منابع پیمانکاری محدود,
we'll go through what you need to know.
آنچه را که شما باید بدانید خواهیم گذراند
I'm Cory Lebson,
من Cory Lebson هستم
author of the UX Careers handbook,
نویسنده کتاب راهنمای شغلی UX,
past president of UXPA, and a long time UX practitioner.
مدیر سابق UXPA ، و یک تمرین کننده طولانی مدت UX.
Join me on LinkedIn Learning
به من در LinkedIn Learning بپیوندید
where we'll talk through all those specialties together,
که در آن در مورد همه تخصص ها با هم صحبت خواهیم کرد,
and explore how you can find the UX support
و چگونه می توانید پشتیبانی UX را پیدا کنید
that you so critically need.
که شما به شدت به آن احتیاج دارید.